deliveroo.com.au 2018-03-10

# Privacy - Deliveroo

Deliveroo Australia Pty Ltd 73 607 915 640 ("we", "our" or "Deliveroo") is committed to protecting the privacy of all visitors to our website deliveroo.com.au and all visitors who access our website or services through any mobile application (together, **"Website"** ). Please read the following privacy policy which explains how we use and protect your information. 

By visiting or ordering services on this Website, you agree and where required you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set out in this policy. 

#### 1\. INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT FROM YOU

  1. When you visit the Website or make a Deliveroo order through the Website, you may be asked to provide information about yourself including your name, address(es), telephone number(s), electronic address(es) and other contact details and payment information such as credit or debit card information. We may also collect transaction details relating to your use of our products, services or benefits, and information about your usage of the Website and information about you from the messages you post to the Website and the e-mails or letters you send to us. 
  2. By accessing Deliveroo information and/or services using mobile digital routes such as (but not limited to) mobile, tablet or other devices/technology including mobile applications, then you should expect that Deliveroo's data collection and usage as set out in this privacy policy will apply in that context too. We may collect technical information from your mobile device or your use of our services through a mobile device, for example, location data and certain characteristics of, and performance data about your device, carrier/operating system including device and connection type, IP address, mobile payment methods, interaction with other retail technology such as use of NFC Tags, QR Codes or use of mobile vouchers. Unless you have elected to remain anonymous through your device and/or platform settings, this information may be collected and use by us automatically if you use the service through your mobile device(s) via any Deliveroo mobile application, through your mobile's browser or otherwise. 
  3. We also collect personal information through our related bodies corporate, our business partners, and third parties who supply services to us. 
  4. We will not collect sensitive information from you or any third party. 
  5. From time to time, you may provide us, and we may collect from you, personal information of a third party (for example, for delivery purposes). Where you provide the personal information of a third party, it is your responsibility to ensure that those persons are aware of this Privacy Policy, understand it and agree to accept it. 
  6. You do not have to provide us with any personal information, however if you do not do so we may not be able to provide you with the products, services or benefits you have requested. 

#### 2\. USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

  1. Your personal information will enable us to provide you with access to the relevant parts of the Website and to supply the services you have requested. It will also enable us to bill you and to contact you where necessary concerning our services. We will also use and analyse the personal information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business, for any other purpose whether statistical or analytical and to help us prevent fraud. Where appropriate, now and in the future you may have the ability to express your preferences around the use of your data as set out in this privacy policy and this may be exercised though your chosen method of using our services, for example mobile, mobile applications or any representation of our Website. 
  2. We will use the personal information we collect for the purpose disclosed at the time of collection, or otherwise as set out in this privacy policy. We wil not use your personal information for any other purpose without first seeking your consent, or where authorised or required by law. 
  3. We may use your personal information to contact you for your views on our services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to the Website or our services. 
  4. Where you have indicated accordingly, you agree that we may use your personal information to let you know about our other products and services that may be of interest to you including services that may be the subject of direct marketing and we may contact you to do so by post, telephone, mobile messaging (e.g. SMS, MMS etc.) as well as by e-mail. 
  5. Where you have indicated accordingly, you agree that we may also share personal information with third parties (including those in the food, drink, leisure, marketing and advertising sectors) to use your information in order to let you know about goods and services which may be of interest to you (by post, telephone, mobile messaging (e.g. SMS, MMS etc.) and/or e-mail) and to help us analyse the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business and services to you. 
  6. If you do not want us to use your data in this way or change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know by using the contact details set out below, amending your profile accordingly, and/or via the unsubscribe function made available to you with each direct marketing communication. 
  7. Please note that by submitting comments and feedback regarding the Website and the services, you consent to us to use such comments and feedback on the Website and in any marketing or advertising materials. We will only identify you for this purpose by your first name and the city in which you reside. 

#### 3\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

  1. Third parties process personal information such as credit card payments and provide support services related to payments for us. In addition, we may need to provide your information to any restaurants ("Partner Restaurants") that you have placed your order with. By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. Deliveroo will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 
  2. If you have consented we may allow carefully selected third parties, including marketing and advertising companies, our affiliates and associates, to send direct marketing to you occasionally about services that may be of interest to you. They may contact you by telephone, SMS as well as by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted by these companies in the future you may opt-out of receiving this information through the unsubscribe function that will be made available to you with each direct marketing communication. 
  3. If our business enters into a joint venture with, purchases or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your personal information may be disclosed or transferred to the target company, our new business partners or owners or their advisors. 
  4. We may use the personal information that you provide to us if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with (and/or where we believe we are under a duty to comply with) any legal obligation; or in order to enforce our Website Terms and any other agreement; or to protect the rights of Deliveroo, Partner Restaurants or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and other organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and prevention. 
  5. We are likely to disclose some of your personal information, for the purposes described above, to organisations in UK & Europe. 
  6. Some of these countries may not have the same or substantially similar privacy laws as those set out in this privacy policy and the Australian Privacy Principles. We may not require organisations to which we disclose personal information in those countries to comply with similar privacy laws, and accordingly your personal information may not receive the same protections that it would in Australia. 
  7. By providing your personal information to us, you consent to our disclosure of your personal information to organisations in those countries even though it may not receive the same protections that it would in Australia. You may request us not to transfer your personal information to the countries listed above, but if you do so we may not be able to provide the services or products you have requested from us. 

#### 4\. SECURITY AND DATA RETENTION

  1. We take steps to protect your personal information from unauthorised access and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will keep your personal information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires. 
  2. Additionally, we take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information when we no longer need it. 
  3. Where you have chosen a password which allows you to access certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We advise you not to share your password with anyone. 
  4. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will take steps to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to the Website and do not accept responsibility for the security of information you send to or receive from us over the internet, or for any unauthorised access or use of that information. Any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. 

#### 5\. ACCESSING AND UPDATING

  1. We will take reasonable steps to make sure that the personal information we collect, use or disclose is accurate, complete and up to date. If your personal details change, such as your address or phone number, please let us know by using the contact details set out below or by amending your profile accordingly. 
  2. You have the right to see the personal information we hold about you ("Access Request") and to ask us to make any changes to ensure that it is accurate and up to date, unless an exception under the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) applies. If you wish to do this, please contact us using the contact details set out below. In the event that you make an Access Request, we may charge a fee for retrieving this information, in which case we will inform you of the fee and obtain your agreement to that fee before providing the information. 
  3. We will promptly acknowledge and investigate any complaint about the way we manage personal information. 

#### 6\. COOKIES

  1. Our website use cookies to track user traffic patterns and to better serve you when you revisit a website. A cookie is a small data file that a website may write to your hard drive when you visit it. A cookie file can contain information, such as a user ID which the website uses to track the pages you have visited. You can refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. However, full functionality for our websites requires the use of cookies. 
  2. Information is also generated whenever a page is accessed on our website that records information such as the time, date and specific page. We collect such information for statistical and maintenance purposes that enables us to continually evaluate our website performance. 

#### 7\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted to the Website and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification. 

#### 8\. CONTACT AND COMPLAINTS

All comments, queries, complaints and requests relating to our use of your personal information are welcomed and should be addressed to: 

The Privacy Officer  
Deliveroo Australia Pty Ltd  
PO Box 336, Balaclava, VIC 3183, Australia  
support@deliveroo.com.au 

We will take reasonable steps to remedy any issues resulting from our failure to comply with our privacy obligations. 

Last Updated October 2015
